Guide to the Bella Abzug papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series XVI: Audio Visual Material
  - Subseries XVI.4: Reel To Reel Tapes
    - Tape #4:
      - Nuclear generation, Women's vote, El Salvadore, Drive to work, Reign in Spain, 11/3/82
      - Women were the winners, NAPAC, Elections, Jobs 11/9/82
      - Unclogging 11/16/82
    - Tape #5:
      - Fathers Day, June 12 march, Budget, Child support, Falklands, 6/16/82
      - ERA setback, voting rights, HUD Federalism 6/21/82
      - Graduation awards, Nuclear Proliferation 6/23/82
      - Book ban, Housing subsidy, ERA, Democratic midterm, Haig 6/29/82
    - Tape #6:
      - Tuition tax credit 4/21/82
      - Budget Impasse, Iran, Cuba,Guatamala and El Salvadore 4/26/82
      - Used Car, Anti- Snoop Law, Women in Government, Ray Donovan, Nuclear Freeze, 5/26/82
      - Nuclear 5-year Plan, Abortion, Big Steel v. Big Mac, What Price Freedom, 5/3/82
    - Tape #7:
      - Employment, What do Women Want, Robots, NASA,and Star Wars, Single issue, 7/7/82
      - Doctors for Disarmament, Abortion 7/13/82
      - Liberation Grove, New Day for ERA 7/21/82
      - Lifting Sanctions, No mandatory 8/20/82
      - School days, Services 9/1/82
      - Civil Rights, Dowry Deaths 9/16/82
    - Tape #8:
      - AFL/CIO Military, 2/19/82
      - Block grant, 3/5/82
      - Nicaragua, Hatch Amendment, 3/19/82
      - Watts reversal, Age discrimination, 2/25/82
      - Secret identity, Oil Prices, Defense offensive, Auto Wages, Child malnutrition, 3/25/82
      - Passover/Easter, 4/7/82
      - El Salvador Election, 4/8/82
      - Nuclear Freezes, 4/9/82
    - Tape #9:
      - Robert Redford, 5/27/82
      - Summit Talks, Enders (?), 6/2/83
      - Jobless, 6/8/83
      - Geneva, Reagan's Women program, 6/9/83
      - Dioxin, Father's Day, Women and Blacks, British elections, Indian Point, 6/15/83
      - Civil Rights, 6/6/83
      - Abortion, 6/7/83
      - Nicaragua, 6/9/83
      - Tax cut gap, 6/13/83
      - Arafat, 6/14/83
    - Tape #10:
      - Japanese/Americans, Cut military spending, Women and Reagan, 3/9/8[?]
      - Freeze in Congress, Satellite sales, Women and Budget, Surveillance, Argentina, 3/11/81
      - Hatch, Central America, Space invaders, 3/29/83
      - Affirmation, Nicaragua, Campaign cost, Product liability 4/6/87
    - Tape #11:
      - Health ins, Raises or Roses, Polls apart, 4/20/83
      - Anti-Nuke info, Freedom of Information, OPEC and Mideast, Women and the '84 Election, 4/27/83
      - Reagan and Central America, 4/28/83
      - Cut military funds, Mother's day, Senate budget battle, Postmark and Peace, Women and Children, 5/15/83
      - Hospice Care 5/13/83
    - Tape #12:
      - WIN, defect, Potomac, Central America, Mideast Peace 4/12/81
    - Tape #13:
      - Women and Work force, 4/27/83
      - Hush money, 4/20/83
      - Lie detectors, 12/13/83
      - AIDS, 5/25/83
      - Budget, 5/23/83
      - Mideast Pullout, 5/26/83
      - Toxic cleanup, 5/13/83
      - Teen contraception
      - MX, 5/23/83
      - Women arid Insurance, 5/24/83
      - Memorial day, gender gap, Williamsburg summit, Auto safe, 5/26/83
    - Tape #13:
      - Israe1 and Sinai, Women and Recession, Ground Zero, National Secretary's Week, 4/21/82
      - Home Sweet Home, Civil Liberties, 4/26/82
      - Energy Fair, Mayday/Human Rights, Ralklands, Women 5/5/82
      - Astronauts, Mother's Day
      - TV and violence, Bidget Gaseball, Life Begins and 40, School Prayer, 5/12/86
    - Tape #15: (Box 1098)
      - Abortion and Federal Employees (ins.), 9/17/80
      - 97th Congress, Family, Moral Majority, Pres. Concession, Jobs, 11/13/81
      - Women's Rights, James Watt, EI Salvador, Inaugural Fashion, Draft, 1/19/81
    - Tape #16:
      - Election, losers, Gallup, Post Election, changes 11/5/80
      - Chanuka, Latin America, 96th Congress, Hit list 12/30/80
      - Elder Abuse, Census Figures, Patrick Gray, Democratic Party, Cabinet appointment, 12/18/80
    - Tape #17:
      - Falkland, Balance Budget 4/12
      - Nuclear First Strike, Tax time, Argentina, Civil Defense, Naval Maneuvers, Ground Hogs, 4/13
    - Tape #18:
      - Poland, Winter shutoffs, Computer games, Family Planning 12/15/81
      - Compo test ban, Modern day wise men, MX/X-mas, social security, Peace on Earth, 12/22/87
      - Increase tax for revenue, Reagan, Losing Midas touch, 12/28/81
    - Tape #19:
      - Rome 8484 12:50 pm, 3/26/83
    - Tape #20:
      - Archive #10 [undated]
    - Tape #21:
      - Teenage contraception, 5/12/82
      - Women and Budget, Courts, El Salvador, War criminals, 5/19/82
    - Tape #22:
      - Gardens and Taxes, Military write-in, 2/9/83
      - Susan B. Anthony, Bush, Fact or Fiction, Toy Soldiers, Sharon, 2/16/83
      - Polluter Gate, Coddling war, Squeal law squelched, Ken Adelman, Jobs bill, 2/23/83
      - International Women's Day, National Gas Prices, Urban Woes, El Salvador, 3/2/83
    - Tape #23:
      - Liberals, Women in Cabinet, Food as Weapon, NY's Drink, Hostages, Martin Luther King Jr., Women's Rights Day, Mass Transit, Republican Inflation, Senate, Rent Control, Defense Dept., Jeans, Corporate taxes, KKK, 12/30/80
    - Tape #24:
      - Democrats and Budget, Social Security, French Elections
      - Mormons and the MX, Freedom of Information Act, [undated]
      - Health care, Elections drink, Hostages, Debate, 10/29/80
      - Time.Magazine Poll 5/5/81
    - Tape #25:
      - Versaille, El Salvador, ERA 6/7/82
    - Tape #26:
      - Acid Rain, Black Power, Tango or Fox Trot 11/16/87
      - Art cuts, Thanksgiving, Bishops and Bombs 11/19/87
      - 5c Gas tax, Military Cuts 12/8/87
      - Gender Gap results 11/9
      - Chilling the Freeze II/II
      - Insurance 11/19
    - Tape #27:
      - Latin America Friends, Sex discrimination 12/8
    - Tape #28:
      - Butter, Labor Day, Hatch and Helms 9/1/82
      - Supply and Demand, First Lady, Prize Winners, PACs, Dow Jones, 9/9/82
      - Over Riding concern, Abortion, Waste Not 9/16/82
    - Tape #29:
      - Tax revolt 8/6/82
      - Helms/Hatch Acts, Anti-Semitism, American Bar, Numbers 8/13/82
      - Please, Civil Defense Working women, MX, Tax increase, 8/20/82
      - Butler 9/1/82
    - Tape #30: (Box 1099)
      - BSA Archive #4 [undated]
    - Tape #31:
      - Liberal Women in Cabinet, Food as Weapon, New Wars Drink, Hostages, [undated]
      - Elder Abuse, Census figures, Patrick Gray, Democratic Party, Cabinet Appointments, 12/13/80
      - Moynihan, Reagan's budget, 96th Congress, Pensions 9/19/80
    - Tape #32:
      - Reagan shooting and Gun control, Women and Budget cuts, 3/3/81
      - Physicians, Nuclear War, Tin Man Awards, KKK, Atlanta Killings
      - El Salvador, book burnings, National Parks, Abuse of Elderly, 4/14/81
      - Polish moratorium
      - Whose Right to Life, Women office workers, Japan and Arms, Robert Sands, El Salvador, 5/5/81
    - Tape #33:
      - Gender gap 6/9/82
      - Citizen's Activism 6/19/82
      - Law of the Sea, El Salvador, Melt Butter Mountain 7/13
      - Balancing act, New Federalism, Fire Dad, Hire Jr. 7/21/8[?]
      - What's New, Tax Cuts, Test Ban, More Poor, No Comment 7/27/8[?]
      - Military Corps, Sex discrimination, India 8/16
    - Tape #34:
      - Medicare, Pay Equity, Jobs bill, Germany, Lame Dicks, Jewish New Year, 9/22/82
      - Single mothers 9/30/82
    - Tape #35:
      - German elections, Central America, "P" rated movies 3/9/83
      - Grenada 3/29/83
      - Jobs 4/5/83 35
      - Campaign costs 4/6/83
      - Holocaust 4/12/83
    - Tape #36:
      - Memorial day 5/26
      - School Lunches 9/30
      - Out of Business, New Rights Scorecard, National Hangover 10/73
      - WIN, unemployment, Congress, Student Default [undated]
      - Names 10/[?]
      - What now, Justice blind, Jewish synagogue, Business, Solidarity, Fair Share, business cut, 10/14
    - Tape #37:
      - New Year Newspaper, Jobs for Women, Military Job Drain 12/28/82
      - 98th Congress, ERA II, Guatamala, Dioxin, Protectionism 1/5/83
      - Women in Cabinet, military missteps 1/17/83
    - Tape #38:
      - Military missteps, 1/17/83
      - Budget blues 1/19/83
      - Teen wages 1/20/83
      - White house valentine, Watt and Indians, saving farms and home 1/21/83
      - Depo Privera 1/24/83
      - Bush in Europe, Infant Mortality, Squeal Law, Hitler, 2/1/83
      - 1984 Budget
      - President and Broadcast Preacher 2/3/83
      - Children's Needs, Jobs Bill, Central America 2/9/83
    - Tape #39:
      - BSA Unmarked [undated]
    - Tape #40:
      - Lennon, Child health, Russia, Women-led families, Fair Housing act 12/9/80
    - Tape #41:
      - BSA Bryant College 10/15/81
    - Tape #42:
      - BSA in Santa Barbara 10/27/84
    - Tape #43:
      - "Flowers from Horseback" 12/27/84
      - BSA in Peoples Republic of China
    - Tape #44:
      - BSA People Are Talking 6/8/8[?]
    - Tape #45: (Box 1100)
      - A.R. Parr Show--Bella and Martin Abzug 10/7/8[?]
    - Tape #46:
      - Issues and Answers--BSA, Clark and Cuffi, 1/14/79
    - Tape #47:
      - BSA--"Nighttimes" 4/11/84
    - Tape #48:
      - BSA--"Over Easy" PHS 2/78
    - Tape #49:
      - People against Nuclear Arms
      - Everybody speaks/with Halston/with Pestman [undated]
    - Tape #50:
      - New York State Democratic Convention 4/12/76
    - Tape #51:
      - Donahue, Monday ([undated])
    - Tape #52:
      - BSA C-Span Call-in, 8/26/83
    - Tape #53:
      - Donahue, 4/17/80
    - Tape #54:
      - Donahue--Gender Gap, [[undated]]
    - Tape #55:
      - "Today In New York" (Manners/BSA, 5/20/82
    - Tape #56:
      - Marti and Bella WNBC/TV, 5/24/82
    - Tape #57:
      - Tomorrow Shaw NBC, 9/17/8[?]
    - Tape #58:
      - BSA Senate Campaign, 6/11/81
    - Tape #59: (Box 1101)
      - Roundtable CNN 1 of 2, 12/26/81
    - Tape #60:
      - Roundtable CNN 2 of 2, 12/26/81
    - Tape #61:
      - "The Gender Gap" [[undated]]
    - Tape #62:
      - "The Gender Gap" four corners [[undated]]
    - Tape #63:
      - BSA at YWCA in Minneapolis Minn--How and why fired from Advisory Council on Women, 2/7/79
    - Tape #64:
      - BSA,7/1/80
    - Tape #65:
      - Gender Gap, 2/6/8[?]
    - Tape #66:
      - BSA, 10/14/80
    - Tape #67:
      - BSA Anti-Semitism, 1/6/80
    - Tape #68:
      - BSA, 12/23/80
    - Tape #69:
      - BSA Master [[undated]]
    - Tape #70:
      - BSA Commentaries, 8/19/8[?]
    - Tape #71:
      - BSA 6 Commentaries, 9/4/80
    - Tape #72:
      - Women USA--Shirley Maclaine, 9/7/84
    - Tape #73:
      - Women USA--Nuclear, 5/28/81
    - Tape #74:
      - Women USA--Vote-Nuclear, 6/12/84
    - Tape #75:
      - Women USA-Reeves, 5/11/82
    - Tape #76: (Box 1102)
      - Women USA-- Reeves, 5/11/82
    - Tape #77:
      - Women USA, 8/4/84
    - Tape #78:
      - Women USA, 8/4/84
    - Tape #79:
      - Women UAS--Nuclear Bomb Spots [undated]
    - Tape #80:
      - Women U SA--Nuclear Bomb Spots [undated]
    - Tape #81:
      - Women USA--Nuclear, 5/28/81
    - Tape #82:
      - ¾ Reel Women USA HAKUHOKO (advertising) (Four Copies), 10/2/84
      - ¾ Reel Women USA Nuclear 5/20/82. Missing
    - Tape #83:
      - ¾ Reel Women's Vote-Diahann Carrol (master) [undated]
    - Tape #84:
      - ¾ Reel Diahanne Carroll [undated]
    - Tape #85:
      - ¾ Reel WNBC PSA Women USA 7/23/84
    - Tapes #86-88 (Box 1102-1103)
      - BSA Commercial # 7A6636 :60 [undated]
      - #7A6646 :60
      - #7A6663 :30
      - PSAs: 06 (Women USA) [undated]
      - PSAs: 06 [undated]
    - Tapes #89-93
      - PSAs: (89-93) :06 12/20/79
      - PSAs: 04 5/1/80
      - PSAs: 04 1980
    - Tape #94:
      - PSA (BSA) :08 1/30/80
    - Tape #95:
      - BSA Feldman and Kahn :60 9/3/79
    - Tape #96:
      - BSA: 30 [undated]
    - Tape #97: (Box 1104)
    - BSA: 60 [undated]
    - Tape #98:
      - BSA :60 [undated]
    - Tape #99:
      - BSA: 30 [undated]
    - Tape #100:
      - BSA: 60 [undated]
    - Tape #101-103:
      - "BSA For Congress," 10/24/86
    - Tape #104: (Box 1105)
      - "BSA For Congress," 10/24/86
    - Tape #105-206:
      - "BSA For Congress," 10/30/86
    - Tape #107:
      - "You don't have to buy the war, Mrs. Smith
    - Tape #108:
      - Today News Service
    - Tape #108:
      - ¾ Reel Lauren Bacall PSA 9/18/84
    - Tape #109:
      - ¾ Reel Women USA PSA's [undated]
- Series XVII: Scrapbooks
  - Scrapbooks and "Direct News 2/5/79-2/9/79" [Vinyl LP] (Box 1106)
  - Scrapbooks (Box 1116)